on in this video I'm going to show you how to add items to your profile that
you can sell to your
clients. So I've logged into my profile and now I'm going to go along here on
the top right and
click on mall. I am now going to click on selling here and this is the page
where you'll manage
all of your items that you have for sale. I don't have any for sale at the
moment so that's why
there's none here. So to add any item just go down here to where it says if you
'd like to sell
something now click here and this is the page that we're going to upload all of
the information
about the item. So the summary I'm going to sell a used/worn pair of panties so
I'm just going to
write that on the summary and we can write a full description so I'm going to
write I wore these
panties all day for you treat yourself to my used panties.
And then we can do a little wink on the end maybe and then down here we can add
photos and even a
movie of the item. So I've taken a picture of myself with the panties on for
the photo. I've
only taken one because just for the purpose of this video I'm going to just
upload this item and
then I'll edit it once I'm done but I think I will end up putting more pictures
on and maybe
even a video because the more the client sees the item the more pictures of it
the more likely
they are to buy it I think. But like I said for the purpose of this video I'm
just going to upload one
so this is the photo I took of myself in the panties. And then up here we can
choose whether we want
to do a normal style or an auction so today we're just going to do a normal
style but if you click
on auction this box these boxes are along here up here and it's basically just
for you to end the
auction and you know how many bits and stuff like that but it's all quite self-
explanatory but for
today we'll just do a normal sale. So quantity is one I just have one pair of
these panties but
you could sell as many as you want. Start date I'm going to click them to start
the start date to be today and the start time to be 2pm because it's half one
now so
I wanted to start at 2pm straight away as soon as I can price for each so I'm
going to put in 15
for 15 credits for this for the used panties. You can have a little think about
what you want
to put for each item and if you need any help with recommendations of what to
sell it each item for
you can ask your mentors or even ask the other girls in the group and we'll all
try and help and
see what we think is best. Another thing you can do is look at the other girls
on the website and
see how much they are selling their things for. You don't really want to um on
to cut yourself
too much but you also don't want to um have your items really expensive because
um yeah if there's
girls on there selling stuff for a lot cheaper then um then yeah if yours are
really expensive
then they might not be sold but you still want to make a good good bit of money
and you still want
to feel like it's worth it so yeah you put in whatever you feel um but we can
help if needs be.
You can also um select a random winner as well where either way we'll select a
random winner
but um this is something you can read up more about and see if you want to do
that I'm not going
to do that one today. So yes I have the item in stock so I'm going to keep that
ticked.
Dispatch timeframe so here this is where you're going to put in um how many
working days after
it's been bought but you're going to dispatch it. I'm going to put in one
working day because I know
that no matter what I can always go and post it the next day well the next
working day. If you're
able to do this I would also recommend doing this and putting in one working
day and obviously
making sure you do dispatch it within that time frame. I think that if um the
client thinks they're
going to get the item a lot sooner they're more likely to buy it where if you
say you're not going
to dispatch it for seven working days for example they might not bother buying
it they might go and
buy from somebody else who can dispatch it faster to them. So yeah if you put
in one two or three days
whatever it is you can you can do um I think that's going to be a good
timeframe for the clients to
to look at when purchasing your product. So here we don't fit any of this out
because this is all
for the auction. And down here is the delivery methods. So you're going to want
to go to the
post office and check first how much it's going to cost to send um send this
item. So let's say
for example you've got a load of used panties and bras and um stockings and
stuff like that you
want to sell. You can go to the post office and see how much it costs to send
to send these items
and then you'll know um for future items that will weigh the same so you don't
have to do it for
every item if that makes sense. So I think it's good to maybe um take all of
these and give the
client options for every single um for every single delivery method because you
might have
clients overseas and you do have to give um recorded and signed for AdultWork
and next day um
AdultWork don't allow you I think it's just recorded and signed for actually
you've got to
um give the client this um option because to help with privacy you know so they
can sign for it
and it's recorded so it's more of a um protecting the client's privacy
basically so it's not going
to get to live in next door or something like that or you know they actually
get it themselves
um so yeah if you do have to do these so I'm just going to put in that every
friend's two
credits I know that it's not well like I said this is just for the purpose of
the video
but you go and check yourself for the post office before doing this
and finally the category so mine is used personal items but this is a good
place to look
if you're thinking what could I sell my clients this is a good place to look at
different ideas
of what to sell them so if you look at the different categories it might give
you an idea of um
of yeah just different things you can you can sell to them now everything seems
like it's done
so I'm going to hit save and this um pops up just to say that you can only sell
items that
can be sent in the mail and obviously I know that used panties can be sent in
the mail so I'm just
going to click OK.